[{"id":"HUMR1","random":690892766,"question":"","category":"Humorous","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Gandalf","pendex":{"Escapist":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Neo","pendex":{"Narcissistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR2","random":755405937,"question":"","category":"Humorous","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"SJP","pendex":{"Social":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Horse","pendex":{"Beastmastery":1,"Reddit":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR3","random":235903495,"question":"","category":"Humorous","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Badluck Brian","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Scumbag Steve","pendex":{"Narcissistic":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR4","random":69922703,"question":"","category":"Humorous","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"Show Case #1","pendex":{"Badluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"Show Case #2","pendex":{"Goodluck":1},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR5","random":789833262,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR6","random":263949325,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR7","random":155447523,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR8","random":804659957,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR9","random":528135847,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR10","random":224613546,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR11","random":606066027,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR12","random":391297362,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR13","random":367208378,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR14","random":829640411,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR15","random":604384578,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR16","random":523804287,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR17","random":828939058,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR18","random":941519013,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR19","random":850381242,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR20","random":864689033,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR21","random":159694071,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR22","random":834302593,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR23","random":24861104,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR24","random":1812365,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR25","random":926071268,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR26","random":64718012,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR27","random":983179412,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR28","random":908299591,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR29","random":368124033,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR30","random":1173745,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR31","random":249541074,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR32","random":438052466,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR33","random":625808381,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR34","random":492875338,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR35","random":896867742,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR36","random":359088348,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR37","random":275695675,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR38","random":396607736,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR39","random":109138095,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR40","random":177911439,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR41","random":967532112,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR42","random":195345763,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR43","random":466270891,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR44","random":540346588,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR45","random":334015456,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR46","random":740706285,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR47","random":266034483,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR48","random":307743407,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]},{"id":"HUMR49","random":762198334,"question":"","category":"","parentid":"","answers":[{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""},{"answer":"","pendex":{},"achievement":"","linkedtype":"","linked":""}]}]
